<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Account Management on PDCA Software</title>
    <link>/support/accountmanagement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Account Management on PDCA Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/support/accountmanagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Account FAQ&#39;s</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/myaccountfaq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/myaccountfaq/</guid>
      <description>Cancellation How do I cancel?Any admin user can go to the My Account section and choose the option Cancel at any time. If I cancel, what happens to the bills?Since payment is in advance, no further bills will be issued.If I cancel, what happens to my access and data?If you cancel, all account usage will be disabled with the exception that any admin user may login during the first 6 months after cancelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activating your trial</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/status/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/status/</guid>
      <description>Trials and Active accounts Trial and active accounts are the same except that an active account is paid for. Follow the instructions below to activate your trial.
A trial account typically lasts for 30 days. At that point it will become dormant and you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to use it. If you are an admin user and you login to a dormant account then you will be offered the opportunity to reactivate the account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Billing</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/billing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/billing/</guid>
      <description>How we calculate your bill. In pdca software, billing is by tier.
On your monthly billing date (at midday GMT), we calculate the amount of users* you have. We then cross check that number with our 3 pricing tiers. We&amp;rsquo;ll then send you an appropriate bill in your chosen currency for the next month.
You will therefore be billed in advance and monthly starting on the same day you signed up so if you convert a trial account to a paid account on the 3rd of November, your first bill will be on the 3rd November and your second on the 3rd December.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Users</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/users/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/users/</guid>
      <description>General Users are counted by the number of users you have with access to our system. The first admin user is created automatically when you initially sign-up. After this they are created only by admin users and admin users can see a list of them in the My Account area.
-&gt; Go to My Account and choose the Users option. User Types Users come in 3 roles, each with different default security settings:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Account</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/myaccount/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/myaccount/</guid>
      <description>My Account is an area where you can manage:
Your account status (trial or active) and price tier. Users Security Your payment methods You can also contact our team about a specific team by using the contact function.
-&gt; Go to the My Account menu option (top right) and choose any of the options to explore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
