<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>intro on PDCA Software</title>
    <link>/tags/intro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in intro on PDCA Software</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/intro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Logging In</title>
      <link>/support/basics/loggingin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/basics/loggingin/</guid>
      <description>How to login -&gt; To login go to the login page The login screen. Email Address Enter your email address :
If you signed up use the same email address as that you signed up with. If an admin user added you, use the email address that they added to your account. If you can&amp;rsquo;t remember the email address you signed up with, check your email programme for your sign-up email.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating your first improvement</title>
      <link>/support/basics/creatingfirst/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/basics/creatingfirst/</guid>
      <description>In pdca, an improvement is a collection of activities that help you improve your organization in some way.
Usually, an improvement starts with a simple idea to make something better in the workplace but the &amp;ldquo;PDCA&amp;rdquo; cycle is inherent within the software. In other words, pdca helps you plan, do, check and act.
Improvement is a general concept and not limited to one type of improvement, workspace or outcome: as such, they can be improvements to things, processes, people, work relationships or indeed anything that improves the organization in some way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Account FAQ&#39;s</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/myaccountfaq/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/myaccountfaq/</guid>
      <description>Cancellation How do I cancel?Any admin user can go to the My Account section and choose the option Cancel at any time. If I cancel, what happens to the bills?Since payment is in advance, no further bills will be issued.If I cancel, what happens to my access and data?If you cancel, all account usage will be disabled with the exception that any admin user may login during the first 6 months after cancelling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activating your trial</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/status/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/status/</guid>
      <description>Trials and Active accounts Trial and active accounts are the same except that an active account is paid for. Follow the instructions below to activate your trial.
A trial account typically lasts for 30 days. At that point it will become dormant and you won&amp;rsquo;t be able to use it. If you are an admin user and you login to a dormant account then you will be offered the opportunity to reactivate the account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All About Users</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/users/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/users/</guid>
      <description>General Users are counted by the number of users you have with access to our system. The first admin user is created automatically when you initially sign-up. After this they are created only by admin users and admin users can see a list of them in the My Account area.
-&gt; Go to My Account and choose the Users option. User Types Users come in 3 roles, each with different default security settings:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is an improvement?</title>
      <link>/support/basics/whatis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/basics/whatis/</guid>
      <description>In pdca, an improvement consists of a logical series of steps or a &amp;ldquo;cycle&amp;rdquo; aimed at improving something in your organization:
An idea or suggestion for an improvement. A plan to implement that idea. A record that the planned improvement was implemented. A check on what happened during implementation. Any lessons learned and potentially a new improvement idea that follows on from the current one. Ideas for improvements can be big or small, theoretical or practical, expensive or cheap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding More Users</title>
      <link>/support/basics/addingusers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/basics/addingusers/</guid>
      <description>How to add a user To add a user you will need to be an admin user.
-&gt; Go to the My Account area, choose users and then add. Fill in the details: the system will send an email to the users email address with a sign-up link. The new user will choose their password during sign-up.
User roles Users can be regular, management or admin users.
Regular users Regular users can add improvements and can change any of the fields in improvements except those restricted to management users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing Improvements</title>
      <link>/support/basics/managing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/basics/managing/</guid>
      <description>How To Manage Improvements If you just want to add a new one:
-&gt; From the home page choose the add option. If you want to view, edit or delete improvements:
-&gt; From the home page choose the improvements option to see a list. To view a single improvement, click on it&#39;s title.You can filter your improvements in order to find a single or group of improvements: -&gt; From the improvements page, use the filters at the top of the list and press enter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Account</title>
      <link>/support/accountmanagement/myaccount/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 14:19:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/support/accountmanagement/myaccount/</guid>
      <description>My Account is an area where you can manage:
Your account status (trial or active) and price tier. Users Security Your payment methods You can also contact our team about a specific team by using the contact function.
-&gt; Go to the My Account menu option (top right) and choose any of the options to explore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
